Indian Neck Folk Festival collection, 1961-2015
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series II: Sound Recordings, 1961-2014
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 10, 1997, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR363)
    DAT 3 of 3. Saturday evening concert featuring Blowout (Deanna Stiles, Sarah Bauhan, Brad Hurley, Sandy David, Connie Hume), DEBO (Deanna Stiles and Bob McQuillen), Colleen Cleveland, Ken Sweeney, Neil and Donna Rossi with Dave Kiphuth, and Cliff Haslam.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1998, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR127)
    Cassette 1 of 2. Indian Neck Folk Festival recording.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1998, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR128)
    Cassette 2 of 2. Indian Neck Folk Festival recording.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 8, 1998, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR364)
    DAT 1 of 2. Saturday evening concert featuring Harvey Tolman, Terry Traub, Shona Rothfield-Carr and friends, Roy Berkeley with Tim Woodbridge, Joan Sprung, Janine and the Levines, the Re-formed Angels (Lisa Neustadt, Irene Saletan, Jim McDade, Sarah Newcomb), Riki Schneyer and the Old Irregular Gospel Bandits, Helen Schneyer, Tim Brown and Matthew Brown, Neil, Donna and Luke Rossi with Susan Sternfold, Robbie Wedeen and Drew Smith, Kossoy Sisters, Rick Lee, Alaina Hammond, Tom Hodgson and Ken Sweeney, Jane Rothfield and Susan Sterngold, and Barbara Carns and Ben Koenig.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 8, 1998, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR365)
    DAT 2 of 2. Saturday evening concert featuring Sandy and Caroline Paton, Don Duncan, Bob McQuillen and Deanna Stiles, Yorkist Ballad Charade Society, Sue West and Friends, Joanie Bronfman, Neal MacMillan, Bob Clayton, Ben Borscht and the Beats, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 8, 1999, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR367)
    DAT 2 of 3. Saturday evening concert with the Lost Acres Bluegrass Persons (Tim and Miki Woodbridge, Richard Blaustein, John Burke), Linda Schrade, Francis Orzechowski and Connor Sleith, Kim Wallach, Total Strangers (Joanie Bronfman, Neil MacMillan, Ann Schunior), Helen Schneyer, Ken Sweeney and Tom Hodgson, the Kossoy Sisters, Neil and Donna Rossi, Caroline Paton, Merritt Herring, Cliff Haslam, Kathy Westra, Barbara Carns and Ben Koenig, Bob Clayton, Gravel Scratchers (Dave Howard, Steve Arking, Richard Blaustein), and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 8, 1999, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR366)
    DAT 1 and 3. Saturday evening concert with the Lost Acres Bluegrass Persons (Tim and Miki Woodbridge, Richard Blaustein, John Burke), Linda Schrade, Francis Orzechowski and Connor Sleith, Kim Wallach, Total Strangers (Joanie Bronfman, Neal MacMillan, Ann Schunior), Helen Schneyer, Ken Sweeney and Tom Hodgson, the Kossoy Sisters, Neil and Donna Rossi, Caroline Paton, Merritt Herring, Cliff Haslam, Kathy Westra, Barbara Carns and Ben Koenig, Bob Clayton, Gravel Scratchers (Dave Howard, Steve Arking, Richard Blaustein), and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1999, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR129)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1999, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR130)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 2000, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR131)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 2000, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR132)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 2000, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR133)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 13, 2000, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR368)
    DAT 1 of 3. Saturday evening concert featuring the Sunset Strugglers (John Burke, Tim and Miki Woodbridge, Richard Blaustein, Dave Kiphuth, Jerry Devokaitis), Liz Downey, Helen Schneyer, Matt Brown, Mark Gilston, Joan Sprung, Rick Lee, Bob McQuillen, Neil and Donna Rossi, Dave Howard, Maggi Peirce, Debby McClatchy, Bob Clayton, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 13, 2000, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR369)
    DAT 2 of 3. Saturday evening concert featuring the Sunset Strugglers (John Burke, Tim and Miki Woodbridge, Richard Blaustein, Dave Kiphuth, Jerry Devokaitis), Liz Downey, Helen Schneyer, Matt Brown, Mark Gilston, Joan Sprung, Rick Lee, Bob McQuillen, Neil and Donna Rossi, Dave Howard, Maggi Peirce, Debby McClatchy, Bob Clayton, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 13, 2000, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR370)
    DAT 3 of 3. Saturday evening concert featuring the Sunset Strugglers (John Burke, Tim and Miki Woodbridge, Richard Blaustein, Dave Kiphuth, Jerry Devokaitis), Liz Downey, Helen Schneyer, Matt Brown, Mark Gilston, Joan Sprung, Rick Lee, Bob McQuillen, Neil and Donna Rossi, Dave Howard, Maggi Peirce, Debby McClatchy, Bob Clayton, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 2001, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR134)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 2001, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR135)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 2001, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR136)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 12, 2001, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR371)
    DAT 1 of 2. Saturday evening concert featuring the Bluegrass Conscripts (Tim and Miki Woodbridge), Ben and Django Koenig, Harvey Tolman and Terry Traub, Rick Lee, Andy May, Helen Schneyer, Ben Borcht and the Beats, Cliff Haslam, Old New England (Bob McQuillen, Jane Orzechowski and Deanna Stiles), Joanie Bronfman, Neal MacMillan, and Ann Schunior, Ballad Charade, Caroline Paton, Liz Downey, Dave Kiphuth and Dave Howard, Richard Blaustein, Steve Arkin, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 12, 2001, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR372)
    DAT 2 of 2. Saturday evening concert featuring the Bluegrass Conscripts (Tim and Miki Woodbridge), Ben and Django Koenig, Harvey Tolman and Terry Traub, Rick Lee, Andy May, Helen Schneyer, Ben Borcht and the Beats, Cliff Haslam, Old New England (Bob McQuillen, Jane Orzechowski and Deanna Stiles), Joanie Bronfman, Neal MacMillan, and Ann Schunior, Ballad Charade, Caroline Paton, Liz Downey, Dave Kiphuth and Dave Howard, Richard Blaustein, Steve Arkin, and others.
  - Vaughn Ward Memorial, ca. 2001, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR358)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 2002, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR137)
    Cassette 1 of 3. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Dick Levine, Ariel Temple, Irene and Ellen, Ken Sweeny, Jamie Carr, Helen Schneyer, Mary LaMarca, Riki Schneyer, Rick Lee, Sugar River Band, Shona and Allan Carr, Alice Backer and Terry Traub, Judy Cook, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 2002, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR138)
    Cassette 2 of 3. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Bennett and Lorraine Hammond, Kathy Westra, Jane Rothfield and Allan Carr, Dave Howard and Steve Arkin, Ali Kiphuth, Bonnie McAllister and Cora Baker, Old New England, Cliff Haslam, Kim Wallach, Ballad Charade, Bob Clayton, Susan Sterngold, Jane Rothfield and Mike Resnick, Maggi Peirce, Ben and Django Koenig, Joe Hickerson, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 2002, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR139)
    Cassette 3 of 3. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Dick Swain and Nancy Matilla, Roustabout, Drew Smith and Robbie Weleen, Donna Rosin and friends, David Jones and Jerry Epstein, Ben Borscht and the Beats, Barbara Carns and Ben Koenig, Harvey Tolman and Terry Traub, Murray Calahan and Ben Koenig, Caroline Paton, George and Thom Ward, Jan Green and Donna Rossi, and April Grant.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 2002, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR373)
    DAT 1 of 3. Saturday evening concert with Tim and Miki Woodbridge, Dave Howard, Dick Levine, Kossoy Sisters, Helen Schneyer, Rick Lee, Kathy Westra, Allison Kiphuth and Linda Schrade, Old New England (Bob McQuillen, Deanna Stiles, Jane Orzechowski), Cliff Haslam, Bob Clayton, Maggi Peirce, Joe Hickerson, Ben Borscht and the Beats, Barbara Carns and Ben Koenig, Caroline Paton, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 2002, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR374)
    DAT 2 of 3. Saturday evening concert with Tim and Miki Woodbridge, Dave Howard, Dick Levine, Kossoy Sisters, Helen Schneyer, Rick Lee, Kathy Westra, Allison Kiphuth and Linda Schrade, Old New England (Bob McQuillen, Deanna Stiles, Jane Orzechowski), Cliff Haslam, Bob Clayton, Maggi Peirce, Joe Hickerson, Ben Borscht and the Beats, Barbara Carns and Ben Koenig, Caroline Paton, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 2002, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR375)
    DAT 3 of 3. Saturday evening concert with the Sugar River Band (the Orzechowskis), Shona and Allan Carr, Helen Schneyer, Old New England (Bob McQuillen, Deanna Stiles, Jane Orzechowski), Tim and Miki Woodbridge, Jane Rothfield with Rick Lee, Sarah Bauhan, Jane Orzechowski and Frank Stettner, Mark Gilston, Caroline Paton, Maggi Peirce, Andy Wallace, Bob Clayton, and Neil Rossi, Ann Schunior, Joanie Bronfman and Neal MacMIllan, Ben and Django Keonig, Sue West, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 2003, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR140)
    Cassette 1 of 4. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Sugar River, Jerry and the Misfits, Shona and Allan Carr, Ariel Temple, Helen Schneyer, Old New England, Tim and Miki Woodbridge, Kate Spencer, Susannah Branch, Harvey Tolman, Kim Wallach, and Norman and Betty MacDonald.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 2003, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR141)
    Cassette 2 of 4. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Jane Rothfield, Rick Lee, Dave Howard and Stacy Phillips, Roger Treat, Tom Gibney, Michael Gibney, Julia Friend, Claire Boucher, the French Connection. Mark Gilston, Caroline Paton, Ben Borscht and the Beats, Yorkist Ballad Charade, Maggi Peirce, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 2003, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR142)
    Cassette 3 of 4. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Neil Rossi, Bob Clayton, Andy Wallace, Pete the Spy, Joy Bennett and Steve Mayer, Donna Rossi, Dick Levine, Triple Play, David Jones, Bob and Megan Stuart, Lucy Simpson, Jerry Epstein, Don Duncan, Ben and Django Koenig.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 2003, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR143)
    Cassette 4 of 4. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Murray Callahan, Kevin Scanlon, Sue West, Susan and Elizabeth Burke, Lorraine and Bennett Hammond.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 2003, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR376)
    DAT 2 of 3. Saturday evening concert with the Sugar River Band (the Orzechowskis), Shona and Allan Carr, Helen Schneyer, Old New England (Bob McQuillen, Deanna Stiles, Jane Orzechowski), Tim and Miki Woodbridge, Jane Rothfield with Rick Lee, Sarah Bauhan, Jane Orzechowski and Frank Stettner, Mark Gilston, Caroline Paton, Maggi Peirce, Andy Wallace, Bob Clayton, and Neil Rossi, Ann Schunior, Joanie Bronfman and Neal MacMIllan, Ben and Django Keonig, Sue West, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 2003, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR377)
    DAT 3 of 3. Saturday evening concert with the Sugar River Band (the Orzechowskis), Shona and Allan Carr, Helen Schneyer, Old New England (Bob McQuillen, Deanna Stiles, Jane Orzechowski), Tim and Miki Woodbridge, Jane Rothfield with Rick Lee, Sarah Bauhan, Jane Orzechowski and Frank Stettner, Mark Gilston, Caroline Paton, Maggi Peirce, Andy Wallace, Bob Clayton, and Neil Rossi, Ann Schunior, Joanie Bronfman and Neal MacMillan, Ben and Django Keonig, Sue West, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 2004, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR378)
    DAT 1 of 3. Saturday evening concert with Shona and Allan Carr, Bob Stuart, Dave Kiphuth and Linda Schrade, SAS (Susannah Branch, Allison Kiphuth, and Shona Carr), the Kossoy Sisters (Irene and Ellen), the Pickers and the Singers (Kathy Torrey, Mark Gilston, Bob McQuillen, Susie Deane, Lorraine Hammond, Kim Wallach, Terry Traub), Sandy and Elizabeth LaPrelle, Helen Schneyer, Mark Gilston, Mary DesRosiers and Connor Sleith, Ralph Bodington, Murray Callahan with Tom Gibney, Jane Rothfield and Allan Carr, Rick Lee with Dave Howard, Tim Woodbridge, and Neil Rossi, Ellen Berkeley, Yorkist Ballad Charade Society, Old New England, Double Play (Robbie Wedeen, Drew Smith, Tim Woodbridge), Sugar River Band, and Judy Cook.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 2004, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR379)
    DAT 2 of 3. Saturday evening concert with Susannah and the All-Boy Band (Rick Lee, Dave Howard, Tim Woodbridge, Neil Rossi, Frank Stettner), David Diamond, Julia Friend and Chloe Moore, Django and Ben Koenig, Harvey Tolman and Terry Traub, David Jones with Tom Gibney and Heather Wood, Roustabout (Bruce Hutton, Lars Hanslin, Chris Romaine, and Jim Bollman), Chris Koldewey, Elizabeth LaPrelle, Neil Rossi, Donna Leiserowitz, Rob Roach, Frank Stettner, Lorraine and Bennett Hammond, Kathy Westra, Wendy Galovich and Terry Traub, Poor Old Horse, Than Ward, Judy Meiselman and Lucy Simpson, Ken Sweeney and Tom Hodgson, Maggi Peirce, Bob Clayton, Caroline Paton, Homer Winslow and friends, and Dick Levine.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 2004, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR380)
    DAT 3 of 3. Saturday evening concert with Joy Bennett with Chris Koldowey, Dave Howard, Heather Wood, Tom Hodgson and Dorry McFarland, Tim Woodbridge and Kate Spencer, and Margaret MacArthur.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 2005, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR381)
    DAT 1 of 3. Saturday evening concert with Shona Carr, Allison Kiphuth, and Susannah Branch, Tom Hogson and Don MacLean, Susannah Branch with Dave Howard and Dave Kiphuth, Bob McQuillen and Kate Spencer, Jane Rothfield and Allan Carr, Elizabeth Burke and Montje Blakovich, Mark Gilston, Tim Woodbridge, Jerry Devokaitis, Matty Levine, and Richard Blaustein, Ben and Django Koenig with Mark Greenberg, Jonathan Leiss, Joyful Noise (Robbie Wedeen, Lucy Simpson, Linda Prager, Judy Meiselman, Drew Smith), Julia Friend, Allan and Shona Carr, Rick Lee, Jane Rothfield and Dave Howard, Old New England, Heather Wood, Lorraine and Bennett Hammond, Joan Sprung and Jane Rothfield, Planet Banjo (John Gersh and Kathy Fletcher), Elizabeth and Sandy LaPrelle, Matty Levine with Dave Kiphuth and Phil Zimmerman.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 2005, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR382)
    DAT 2 of 3. Saturday evening concert with Dick Levine, Chloe Maher, David Jones with Jerry Epstein, Bob and Juno Stuart, Bob and Megan Stuart, Murray Callahan, Andy Wallace, Sugar River Band (the Orzechowskis), North Country Sapsuckers (Sarah Bauhan and Frances and Sophie Orzechowski), Claire Boucher and Brad Hurley, Wendy Galovich and Kate Spencer, Charlie Ipcar with Tom Hall, Linn Schulz and Barry Finn, Neil and Donna Rossi with Frank Stettner and Dave Kiphuth, Peter McHugh with Connie and Jack Hume and Frank Stettner, Dave Kiphuth and Linda Schrade, Gospel Sparrows (Larry Marschall, Phil Zimmerman, Mark Greenberg), Ken Sweeney and Tom Hodgson, Michael Gibney, Dave Howard with Frank Stettner, Roustabout (Bruce Hutton, Lars Hanslin), Triple Play (Tim Woodbridge, Robbie Wedeen, Drew Smith, Frank Stettner), Clarice Kierjuff and Jerry Epstein, and Sharon Krause.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 2005, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR383)
    DAT 3 of 3. Saturday evening concert with Pete the Spy, Ernie the Spy, and Jean Pauly-Jennings.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 2006, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR384)
    DAT 1 of 3. Saturday evening concert with Old New England, Allan Carr, Dan Milner, Joy Bennett, Ralph Bodington, Claire Boucher and Brad Hurley, Bonnie Milner, Harvey Tolman, Linn Schulz and Tom Hall, Mark Gilston, Elizabeth Burke, the HazMats (Tim Woodbridge, John Burke, Steve Arkin, Jerry Devokaitis), Rick Lee, Ken Sweeney, Jeri Corlew, Jeremy Brecher, Susannah Branch, Chris Koldewey, Bob Stuart, Joanie Bronfman, Neal MacMillan, and Ann Schunior.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 2006, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR385)
    DAT 2 of 3. Saturday evening concert with Tom Hall and Linn Schulz, Kathy Westra, Sugar River Band (the Orzechowskis) with Sarah Bauhan, David Jones, Yorkist Ballad Charade (not recorded), 40 Acres and a Mule, George Stephens and Mary LaMarca, Sue West and Ann Schunior, Allison Kiphuth and Linda Schrade, Joe Hickerson, Robbie Wedeen, Drew Smith, Linda Prager, and Judy Meiselman, Doubleplay (Drew Smith and Robbie Wedeen), Barry Finn, Lorraine and Bennett Hammond with Phil Zimmerman and Dave Kiphuth, Poor Old Horse (David Jones, Heather Wood, Michael Gibney), Bill Quimby, Mark Greenberg, Ben and Django Koenig, John Roberts, Nathaniel Ward, Josh Vertiel, Murray Callahan, Ernie the Spy and Juno Stuart, Charmion Chaptin-Thomas, and Edmund Thomas.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 2006, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR386)
    DAT 3 of 3. Saturday evening concert with Heather Wood, Phil Zimmerman, Dick Levine, Pete the Spy, Pamela Goddard, Caroline Paton, and Jonathan Leiss.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 12, 2007, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR387)
    DAT 1 of 3. Saturday evening concert with Jacqui Morse and Jeri Corlew, Shona and Allan Carr, Ralph Bodington, Dick Levine, Matty Levine, David Levine, and Janine Levine, Ken Sweeney, Jonathan Leiss and Becca Robinson, Anything Goes (Ben Koenig, Mark Greenberg), Ryan and Brennish Thompson, Breatrix and Claude Methe, Lorraine and Bennett Hammond, Old New England, Sue West, Joanie Bronfman, Neal MacMillan, and Ann Schunior, Jerry Devokaitis and Tim Woodbridge, Allison Kiphuth and Linda Schrade, Joy Bennett and Chris Koldewey, Bob Stuart, Susannah Branch, and Planet Banjo (Jon Gersh, Kathy Fletcher).
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 12, 2007, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR388)
    DAT 2 of 3. Saturday evening concert with Kathy Westra, Ernie the Spy and Jono Stuart, Kim Wallach, Spare Parts Quartet (Kate Spencer, Susannah Branch, Tim Woodbridge, Don Duncan), Jane Rothfield and friends, Sugar River Band (the Orzechowskis), Lisa Null, Ben Borscht and the Beats (Drew Smith, Mike Resnick, Susan Sterngold), Maggi Peirce, Mick Lane, Caroline Paton, Edmund Thomas and Charmion Chaplin Thomas, David Jones and Jerry Epstein, Trish Miller and John Kirk, Pamela Goddard, Foggy Mountain Boys (Phil Zimmerman, Larry Marschall, Neil Rossi, Frank Stettner, Mark Greenberg), Double Play (Robbie Wedeen, Mike Resnick, Drew Smith, Larry Marschall), Julia Friend, and Murray Callahan.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 12, 2007, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR389)
    DAT 3 of 3. Saturday evening concert with Pete the Spy, Heather Wood and Ken Schatz, Chloe Maher and Nora Smith, Dave Howard and Frank Stettner, Joyful Noise (Judy Meiselman, Linda Prager, Robbie Wedeen, Drew Smith, Mike Resnick), Bonnie Milner, Bruce Hutton, Judy Cook, Jane Rothfield and Susan Sterngold.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 10, 2008, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR390)
    DAT 1 of 3. Saturday evening concert with Joan Sprung, Ralph Bodington, Jamie Rothfield-Carr with Jane Rothfield, Susan Sterngold, and Linda Schrade, Sarah Bauhan, Sophie and Neil Orzechowski, Mark Gilston, Kenal and Jacqui Morse, Brennish and Ryan Thompson, Cliff Haslam, Joanie Bronfman, Neal MacMillan, and Ann Schunior, Mary Lamarca, George Stephens, and John Roberts, Blast from the Past (Dave Kiphuth, Dave Howard, Frank Stettner, Neil Rossi, Phil Zimmerman), Dave Kiphuth and Linda Schrade, Susan and Elizabeth Burke, Ben Koenig, Claire Boucher and Brad Hurley, Dave Howard and Frank Stettner, Chloe Maher and Nora Smith, Andy May and Rick Lee, and Joy Bennett and Chris Koldewey.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 10, 2008, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR391)
    DAT 2 of 3. Saturday evening concert with Hen's Teeth (Jane Rothfield, Linda Schrade, Allan Carr, Dave Kiphuth), Ken Sweeney, Sugar River Band, Megan Stuart Rogers and Bob Stuart, Susannah Branch and Dave Howard, Heather Wood, Short One Sister (Kim Wallach and Kate Seeger), Sakura Taiko (Smack and Lolo Walser), Old New England, Shona Rothfield-Carr, Burke Family, Bob Clayton, Caroline Paton, Bob Stuart, Lorraine and Bennett Hammond, Frank Stettner, and Bob Stuart, Shingle the Roof (Kate Spencer, Tim Woodbridge, Jerry Devokaitis), John Roberts and Lisa Preston, Kate Spencer, and Mick Lane.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 10, 2008, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR392)
    DAT 3 of 3. Saturday evening concert with Kathy Westra, Harvey Tolman and Bob McQuillen, Robbie Wedeen, Drew Smith, Mike Resnick, Tim Woodbridge, Ben Borscht and the Beats (Drew Smith, Mike Resnick, Susan Sterngold), Edmund and Charmion Thomas, Brian Cartwright, Joyful Noise and Jerry Epstein (Robbie Wedeen, Barbara Meiselman, Linda Prager), Dick Levine, and Charlie Baum.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 2009, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR393)
    DAT 1 of 2. Saturday evening concert with Tim Woodbridge and Friends of Roy Berkeley, Old New England, Johnson Girls, Sandy and Elizabeth LaPrelle, Ralph Bodington, NERS (Neil Orzechowski, Emma Clarkson, Russell Orzechowski, Sarah Bauhan), David Jones with Jerry Epstein, Brian Cartwright, Susie Deane and Frank Stettner, Red Hen, Mark Gilston, Murray Callahan, Neal MacMillan, Shingle the Roof, Rick Lee, Dick Levin and John Roberts, Morphic Resonance (Neil Rossi, Susan Sternhold, Mike Resnick), Dan Milner with David Jones and the Johnson Girls, Kathy Westra, Sugar River Band, Julie Sorcek, Lorraine and Bennett Hammond, Tom Hodgson and Ken Sweeney, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 2009, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR394)
    DAT 2 of 2. Saturday evening concert with Ken Schatz and Barry Finn, Robbie Wedeen, Drew Smith and Frank Stettner, Clarice Kjerluff, Matt Brown, Old Town Road (The Stuart Family, Bob and Megan), Bob Clayton, Pamela Goddard, Ben Borcht at the Beats, Anna Nowogrodzki and Ian McGullam, Edmund Thomas, Elizabeth Burke, The Night Visitors (Judy Meiselman, Linda Praeger, Penny Anderson, Robbie Wedeen), Rick Mohr, Maggie Bye, Phil Zimmerman, Larry Marschall's Bluegrass Vertebrates, Dave Howard, Caroline Paton, Terry Dignon, Don McLean and Tom Hodgson, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 2010, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR395)
    DAT 1 of 2. Saturday evening concert with Old New England, Judy Cook, Elizabeth and the Girl Band (Elizabeth Burke, Jane Rothfield, Linda Schrade), Shona Carr and Sam Forrest Stallings, Ryan and Brennish Thompson, Bob Clayton, Susie Deane, Chris Carpenter, Frank Stettner, Dick Levine, Neil Rossi, Norris Bennett, Glyn Collinson, Anything Goes (Ben Koenig, Mark Greenberg), Jonathan Leiss, Phil Zimmerman, Shingle the Roof (Tim Woodbridge, Kate Spencer, Jerry Devokaitis) with Beck Hartman-Berrier, David Jones, Caroline Paton, Joanie Bronfman, Heather Wood, George Stephens, Ken Schatz, and others.